[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Which of these is NOT a former name of Sri Lanka?",
        "correctAnswer": 4,
        "category": 1,
        "answers": {
            "answer_1": "Taprobane",
            "answer_2": "Ceylon",
            "answer_3": "Lanka",
            "answer_4": "Vedda"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "In what year did Sri Lanka become independent from Britain as the Dominion of Ceylon?",
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "category": 1,
        "answers": {
            "answer_1": "1948",
            "answer_2": "1947",
            "answer_3": "1949",
            "answer_4": "1946"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Which of these colours is NOT featured on Sri Lanka&#39;s national flag?",
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "category": 1,
        "answers": {
            "answer_1": "Black",
            "answer_2": "Yellow",
            "answer_3": "Green",
            "answer_4": "Orange"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What natural disaster hit Sri Lanka on Boxing Day 2004?",
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "category": 1,
        "answers": {
            "answer_1": "Tsunami",
            "answer_2": "Flood",
            "answer_3": "Hurricane",
            "answer_4": "Famine"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Which of these Sri Lankan cities is NOT on the coast?",
        "correctAnswer": 3,
        "category": 1,
        "answers": {
            "answer_1": "Galle",
            "answer_2": "Colombo",
            "answer_3": "Kandy",
            "answer_4": "Jaffna"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "question 6",
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "category": 2,
        "answers": {
            "answer_1": "answer 1",
            "answer_2": "answer 2",
            "answer_3": "answer 3",
            "answer_4": "answer 4"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "question 7",
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "category": 2,
        "answers": {
            "answer_1": "answer 1",
            "answer_2": "answer 2",
            "answer_3": "answer 3",
            "answer_4": "answer 4"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "question 8",
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "category": 2,
        "answers": {
            "answer_1": "answer 1",
            "answer_2": "answer 2",
            "answer_3": "answer 3",
            "answer_4": "answer 4"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "question 9",
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "category": 2,
        "answers": {
            "answer_1": "answer 1",
            "answer_2": "answer 2",
            "answer_3": "answer 3",
            "answer_4": "answer 4"
        }
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "question 10",
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "category": 2,
        "answers": {
            "answer_1": "answer 1",
            "answer_2": "answer 2",
            "answer_3": "answer 3",
            "answer_4": "answer 4"
        }
    }
]